jaysxlist.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy

The JaysXList Classifieds Listing Privacy Policy describes how our website handles your personal information. We guarantee to protect all your personal information and also not to disclose them to a third party unless specified. Our main goal is to take care of your personal information and in this manner we guarantee to keep all your personal information safe and private. The JaysXlist website collects and stores personal information such as:

  * Phone numbers, addresses, emails, physical contact information, and sometimes financial information
  * Statistic on page view, traffic to our website, sign in data, ad data. This is done through the use of cookies which can be disables if needed by the user in the browser
  * Other information such as users IP address and web log information

JaysXList uses your personal information in order to provide you with our services. We also use your personal information in cases of potential disputes which need to be addressed, to collect fees and troubleshoot problems. Your personal information are also used so we could provide a safe trading environment and to enforce our policies. This privacy policy is also designed to help us to provide our users with a better service and to improve their experience. We use the personal information provided by the users to reach target audience, for service updates and to deliver promotional offers according to personal needs (deliver other things to users as described).

The JaysXList Classifieds doesn’t sell or rent personal information to other parties for marketing needs without consent from the user. We may disclose personal information in order to respond to legal requirements or to claims when a posting violate other’s rights, to protect person’s rights/property/safety or to enforce our policies. We may also disclose information with third party websites and publishers so the ads can be published on other websites or online platforms.

The JaysXList Classifieds may allow you to use third party sign in credentials to sign in into our website and with you permission we may import other information contained in your third party profile. We may also provide you with an opportunity to import information about your connections at your discretion.

You agree to receive emails from our service unless you specify otherwise. If you don’t agree to this type of communication then you should emphasize your preference. You may not be able to use our website to take addresses, send spam or in any other way breach our terms and Privacy Policy. WE reserve the right to automatically scan and filter email messages sent through our communication tools to identify malicious content and other forbidden content. You can report spam by contacting us.

You can see, modify or delete any of your personal information. The JaysXlist.com reserves the right to hold all personal information as they needed to resolve disputes, enforce our policies and prevention.

JaysXlist uses tools such as encryption, physical security and passwords to protect the users’ personal information. However, we can’t guarantee this completely!

We use cookies to help analyze our web page traffic, customize and improve our service, analyze promotional effectiveness.
